The/O fate/O of/O Lehman/ORGANIZATION Brothers/ORGANIZATION ,/O the/O beleaguered/O investment/O bank/O ,/O hung/O in/O the/O balance/O on/O Sunday/O as/O Federal/ORGANIZATION Reserve/ORGANIZATION officials/O and/O the/O leaders/O of/O major/O financial/O institutions/O continued/O to/O gather/O in/O emergency/O meetings/O trying/O to/O complete/O a/O plan/O to/O rescue/O the/O stricken/O bank/O ./O 
Several/O possible/O plans/O emerged/O from/O the/O talks/O ,/O held/O at/O the/O Federal/ORGANIZATION Reserve/ORGANIZATION Bank/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION New/ORGANIZATION York/ORGANIZATION and/O led/O by/O Timothy/PERSON R./PERSON Geithner/PERSON ,/O the/O president/O of/O the/O New/ORGANIZATION York/ORGANIZATION Fed/ORGANIZATION ,/O and/O Treasury/ORGANIZATION Secretary/O Henry/PERSON M./PERSON Paulson/PERSON Jr./PERSON ./O 
